Ryan Jonah

Software Developer

With a lifelong passion for technology and years of experience assisting customers through a myriad of different issues, this dedicated problem solver is willing to face every new prospect with an adamant determination towards finding solutions.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance, Moncton, NB— Software Developer

September 2021 - Present

 I am currently building a website for Whispering Willow; a wedding venue located in south-eastern New Brunswick.

Cloud5, Minto, NB— Customer Service Representative

January 2017 - August 2020 January 2014 - February 2015

- Selling, creating, and canceling hotel reservations across multiple accounts covering hundreds of properties internationally.
- Helping customers resolve issues via phone and email by way of information gathering, internal systems processing, reviewing hotel and company policies, and consulting hotel staff directly.
- Assisting customers with billing inquiries while following Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliance.
- Assisting other call center representatives through escalation calls while fulfilling the rotational role of shift supervisor.
- Assisting customers through the navigation of various hotel websites.
- Assisting other call center representatives in troubleshooting technical issues.

EDUCATION

NBCC, Moncton, NB— Web and Mobile Application Development

September 2020 - June 2021

Coder Foundry, Kernersville, NC— Coding Bootcamp

June 2021 - September 2021

43 Harts Lake Road Gagetown, NB E5M 1L7 (506) 327-5298 ryan c jonah@yahoo.ca

Portfolio LinkedIn Github

SKILLS

C#

ASP.NET

Entity Framework

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Bootstrap

React

Git

Python

LINQ

MS SQL Server

Windows OS

Linux OS

Bash

Customer Service

Sales

LANGUAGES

English

Hobbies

Technology, fitness, writing, philosophy, science, history, music, cooking, video games